

An Hoang Long (Mr.)

FRESHER TESTER

PROFILE -

- 0854890904
- annhlong197@gmail.com
- P Hoang Hoa Tham, Ba Dinh, Hanoi

SKILLS -

ANALYSIS, REPORT

- Analyze SRS documentation, log Q&A.
- Synthesize and evaluate, reporting test results.

WORKFLOW MANAGEMENT

- Prioritize work order.
- Be disciplined, ensuring project progress.

OFFICE INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

- Basically using Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, Powerpoint.

OBJECTIVE

Throughout the following two years, I am to gain practical experience, enhance my technical abilities, and grow my career in the field of software testing.

Subsequently, after obtaining ISTQB Foundation Level certification and establishing a solid foundation of Automation tests, I will challenge myself with the QC position, while ensuring high-quality standards and continuous improvement.

WORK EXPERIENCE -

TESTER 03/2023 - 05/2023

CODESTAR ACADEMY

1/ Projects:

- Project 1: "Courses Management" Website Development: Functions testing "General assessment management", "Courses assessment management", "Assessment synthesis".
- + Execute tests: the UI, datepicker fields, dropdown list fields; feature of "Calculating average for class", "Searching with filters", "Class rating".
- Project 2: "CodeStar Users Management" Website Development: Function testing "Add new user".
- + Execute tests: the UI, information fields (Full name, password, email, phone number, user ID), dropdown list fields.
- **Project 3:** "Courses Information Look-up" Application Development: Functions testing "SIGN UP", "SIGN IN", "LOG OUT", "Searching course information".
 - + Execute tests: the UI, information fields, buttons.

2/ Knowledge:

- Find out, analyze project requirements, log Q&A.
- Write testing documents (test cases, test data,...).
- Execute base on written cases testing, using testing techniques: Smoke testing,
 Sanity testing, Comfirmation testing, Regression testing.
 - Query datas in the Database with basic commands by MySQL.
 - Basic API testing.
 - Bugs reportation on Jira tool.
 - Re-test after bugs fixed.

3/ Test cases link:

https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1g-slyLqd-I1ZT2t8jsmQXK7nu_3QbCL/edit#gid=1592439959

https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/136ar3Y28RtMf3fTx3d5QJHjCU5ZMafi9/edit t # gid=1031673527

SALES ADMIN 06/2022 - 04/2023

VIETNAM VITALYTI MEDICAL .,JSC

- Ensuring quality in process of goods supply and handling troubleshoot problems.
- Customer information censorship, manage of sales datas by area in charge.
- Contracts management, disseminate promotions to customers.
- Making push-sales plan.
- Sales statistics, collecting business datas to identify potential customers.

EDUCATION -

THE DEGREE OF PHARMACIST

07/2015 - 07/2020

Dainam University

CERTIFICATIONS

© topcv.vn